mycutegames.com 2019-04-21

# PrivacyPolicy - My Cute Games

**LAKTA GROUP, CORP. PRICACY POLICY**

Last updated: September 29, 2015

This privacy statement describes information gathering and dissemination practices. By accessing and/or using our web sites, you accept this privacy statement and agree to the terms, conditions and notices contained or referenced herein. We may modify this privacy statement from time to time. When posting changes to this privacy statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this page.

**COLLECTED INFORMATION AND ITS USE**

**Personally Identifiable Information**

We do not collect your personally identifiable information, except for your name and e-mail you have provided to us by using the “contact form”. We use your name and e-mail only for the purpose of sending replay to your request submitted to us. This personally identifiable information is not released to any non-Affiliate third party without your prior consent except as provided herein. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information to respond to law enforcement requests, or where required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web sites, or to protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public. To safeguard the confidentiality and security of your personally identifiable information, we may use industry standard practices and technologies including but not limited to firewalls, encrypted transmission and data encryption of sensitive personal and/or financial information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you use these services at your own risk.  

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We may collect technical information about your device. Such non-personally identifiable information may be used to personalize your experience and to deliver targeted advertising and promotional offers to you.  We may share some of this information for our own analysis and research purposes with our professional advisors or consultants and third party partners.

**Sign Up information**

Any information you provide to us, and any information you choose to share about yourself as part of your use of our web sites, may be stored as entered.

**Cookies:**

We do not use Cookies on our web sites. Cookies are text files of information that a web site places on the device for recognizing the visitor’s browser and providing certain personalized features like targeted advertising and promotional offers. To serve ads in services where cookie technology may not be available (for example, in mobile applications), we may use anonymous identifiers that perform similar functions to cookies. We may use ad network providers to help present advertisements on our websites. These ad network providers use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to help the presenting, better targeting, and measuring of the effectiveness of their advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audiences. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by such third parties as ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not this privacy statement. Specifically the use of the cookies by Google® Inc. is governed by <http://google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners>. You can opt out of receiving cookies from certain third-party advertising networks by resetting your browser. You may also use the link <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin> to the cookie opt-out page. However, some features and services may not function properly if cookies are disabled.

**Aggregated, Anonymous Information:**

We may collect aggregated, anonymized information via our web sites that does not identify any single user.

**SHARING INFORMATION**

**Affiliates:**

We may share our data with our parent, subsidiary and other affiliated companies (each an "Affiliate") and as described below.  To the extent that these Affiliates have access to your personally identifiable information, they will give such information at least the same level of protection and treat it at least as protectively as they give to treat information they obtain from their other users.  Our Affiliates will follow privacy practices no less protective of all users than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. 

**Third Party Service Providers:**

We may disclose your personal information as well as aggregate, anonymous information to third party business partners and third parties who perform services for us, such as billing processing, collecting, storing and analyzing data, providing search results and links, and providing advertising and marketing assistance. Those third parties have access to your information only as necessary to perform their functions, and for no other purposes.

**THIRD PARTY SITES**

If you access our web sites via a third party marketplace, such as App Store, Google Play, that third party marketplace may collect information about you or receive information from us in order to provide or analyze its services. In addition, third parties that serve advertisements within our web sites, as well as third party links to or from our web sites, may collect information about you. Except as otherwise expressly described in this privacy statement, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you.  To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are on our web sites, including links to third party sites, or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Since we do not control the privacy policies of any third parties, and is not responsible for the information submitted to or collected by third parties, you should review those third party privacy policies to understand the way your information may be collected and handled by such third parties.

**CHILDREN**

We do not offer products for purchase by children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If you are under 13, you may use and access our web sites only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

We are committed to the protection of children’s online privacy and compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us via email at [laktagr@gmail.com](mailto:laktagr@gmail.com). We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13.

**CONTACT US**

To review, modify or remove the information you have provided to us, or to contact us with any questions or complaints, please email us at [laktagr@gmail.com](mailto:laktagr@gmail.com).
